https://www.pengate.com/privacy-policy

Locations
York, PA (Corporate Office)
Locations
York, PA (Corporate Office)
----------------------------------
Pengate Handling Systems, Inc. operates the domain https://www.pengate.com. This page details our policy regarding the collection, utilization and disclosure of personal user information received via this website. All personal information is strictly used to provide content for and improve upon the website itself. By using this site, you agree to the collection and use of personal information in accordance with this policy.
Data Collection And Usage
While using this website, you may provide us with certain personally-identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally-identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name or company.
Data Logging
Like many website operators, we collect information your browser transmits when you visit our domain. This data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser version, the subpages you visit, the time spent on those subpages, the time and date of your visit, and other similar statistics. In addition, we may use third-party services such as Google Analytics to collect, monitor, and analyze this data.
Communication
If authorized, we may use your personal information to contact you via newsletter or other promotional vehicle. We fully adhere to and respect any subscription requests we may receive from you.
Cookies
Cookies are files that collect small amounts of data and typically contain an anonymous, unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser when you visit a website, and are stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many company websites, www.pengate.com enables cookies to collect certain information. You may instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If your device does not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to access some portions of this site.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. Keep in mind, however, that no method of digital transmission or electronic storage via the internet is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially-acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes
This version of our Privacy Policy is effective as of 7/1/2016, and will remain in effect until further provisions are made. Any subsequent changes to this policy will be in effect immediately following publication to this page. Pengate Handling Systems reserves the right to update or change this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of this website following any modifications to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of said modifications. If
any material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, Pengate will notify users via email
or by displaying prominent verbiage on www.pengate.com.
Please Contact Us if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy.
